customergauge.com 2018-10-11

# Privacy Policy | CustomerGauge

CustomerGauge (or the “Company”), known as CustomerGauge and CustomerGauge USA LLC and Directness BV, is committed to protecting the privacy of individuals who visit the Company’s Web Sites and individuals who register to use the Services as defined below. This Privacy Statement describes CustomerGauge’s privacy practices in relation to the use of the Company’s Web sites and the related applications and services offered by CustomerGauge (the “Services”).  

 **1\. Web Sites Covered**

This Privacy Statement covers the information practices of Web Sites and Services that link to this Privacy Statement, including: https://customergauge.com, https://*.customergauge.com, [](https://npsbenchmarks.com/)[https://npsbenchmarks.com](https://npsbenchmarks.com/) etc (collectively referred to as “CustomerGauge Web Sites” or “the Company’s Web Sites”).

CustomerGauge Web sites may contain links to other Web sites. The information practices or the content of such other Web sites are governed by the privacy statements of such other Web sites. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of other Web sites to understand their information practices.

 **2\. Information Collected**

CustomerGauge collects individually-identifiable information (“Personal Information”) from individuals who visit CustomerGauge Web Sites (“Web Site Visitors”), individuals who are invited to complete CustomerGauge Surveys (“Survey Users”) and individuals employees or contractors employed by CustomerGauge Clients (“Clients”) that use the Services (“Client Users” or “Customers”)

CustomerGauge may contact you as a Survey User on behalf of Clients, using the Clients’ branding and Email addresses. CustomerGauge acts in the role of the Data Processor (“Data Processor”) on behalf of Client (“Data Owner”) that has provided information to CustomerGauge and will consume the data collected. In all cases, CustomerGauge has obtained permission from the Clients in order to contact you. CustomerGauge will notify the Data Owner if you request information on Client’s respective Privacy Policy or in the case of “Unsubscribe” or “Do not contact” notifications.

When expressing an interest in obtaining additional information about the Services or registering to use the Services, CustomerGauge requires you to provide the Company with personal contact information, such as name, company name, address, phone number, and email address (“Required Contact Information”). When purchasing the Services, CustomerGauge may require you to provide the Company with financial qualification and billing information, such as billing name and address, credit card number, and the number of employees within the organization that will be using the Services (“Billing Information”). CustomerGauge may also ask you to provide additional information, such as company annual revenues, number of employees, or industry (“Optional Information”). Required Contact Information, Billing Information, and Optional Information about Customers are referred to collectively as “Data About CustomerGauge Customers”.

As you navigate the Company’s Web sites, CustomerGauge may also collect information through the use of commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as Cookies and Web Beacons (“Web Site Navigational Information”). Web Site Navigational Information includes standard information from your Web browser (such as browser type and browser language), your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, and the actions you take on the Company’s Web sites (such as the Web pages viewed and the links clicked).

 **3\. Use of Information Collected**

The Company uses Data given by Survey Users to help Clients better understand customer issues and to ultimately create better customer experiences.  CustomerGauge compiles reports statistics and generates other electronic contacts to assist Clients which may use this information to contact you in order to improve your experience or to learn more from you.

When expressing an interest in CustomerGauge services, the Company uses Data provided by  CustomerGauge Customers to perform the services requested. For example, if you fill out a “Contact Me” Web form, the Company will use the information provided to contact you about your interest in the Services.

The Company may also use Data provided by CustomerGauge Customers for marketing purposes. For example, the Company may use information you provide to contact you to further discuss your interest in the Services and to send you information regarding the Company, its affiliates, and its partners, such as information about promotions or events.

CustomerGauge uses  Billing Information solely to check the financial qualifications and collect payment for the CustomerGauge Services.

CustomerGauge uses Web Site Navigational Information to operate and improve the Company’s Web sites. The Company may also use Web Site Navigational Information alone or in combination with Data About CustomerGauge Customers to provide personalized information about the Company

 **4\. Web Site Navigational Information**

CustomerGauge uses commonly-used information-gathering tools, such as Cookies and Web beacons, to collect information as you navigate the Company’s Web sites (“Web Site Navigational Information”). This section describes the types of Web Site Navigational Information used on the Company’s Web sites and how this information may be used.

 **Cookies** : CustomerGauge uses Cookies to make interactions with the Company’s Web sites easy and meaningful. When you visit one of the Company’s Web sites, CustomerGauge servers send a cookie to your computer. Standing alone, cookies do not personally identify you; they merely recognize your Web browser. Unless you choose to identify yourself to CustomerGauge, either by responding to a promotional offer, opening an account, or filling out a Web form (such as a “Contact Me”), you remain anonymous to the Company. CustomerGauge uses cookies that are session-based and persistent-based. Session cookies exist only during one session, i.e., only while you are reading or navigating the Company’s Web Sites. They disappear from your computer when you close your browser software or turn off your computer. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after you close your browser or turn off your computer. Please note that if you disable your Web browser’s ability to accept cookies, you will be able to navigate the Company’s Web sites, but you may not be able to successfully use the Services.

Cookies that are used as part of the Services (in the proxy) may include cookies of a third party Web site that is being co-browsed, for example, in order to deliver the Web site as intended by the third party Web site operator. The cookie practices of such Web sites are governed by their own respective privacy statements. The Company encourages you to review the privacy statements of other Web sites to understand their information practices.

 **Web Beacons:**  CustomerGauge, or third parties with whom we contract, may use Web beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about Customers and Visitors’ usage of the Company’s Web sites and interaction with emails from the Company. Web beacons are clear electronic images that can recognize certain types of information on your computer, such as cookies, when you viewed a particular Web site tied to the Web beacon, and a description of a Web site tied to the Web beacon. For example, CustomerGauge may place Web beacons in marketing emails that notify the Company when you click on a link in the email that directs you to one of the Company’s Web sites. CustomerGauge uses Web beacons to operate and improve the Company’s Web sites and email communications.

 **IP Addresses and URLs:  **Due to Internet communications standards, when you visit or use CustomerGauge Web sites, we automatically receive the URL of the Web site from which you came and the Web site to which you go when you leave a CustomerGauge Web site. We also receive your computer’s Internet Protocol (IP) address (or the proxy server you use to access the World Wide Web), your computer operating system, the type of Web browser you are using, and your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This information is used to analyze overall trends to help us improve the CustomerGauge Service and to track and aggregate non-personal information. For example, CustomerGauge uses IP addresses to monitor the regions from which Customers and Visitors navigate the Company’s Web sites.

CustomerGauge may collect aggregated data regarding use of the CustomerGauge Services, including, without limitation, number of visitors to the Web site, frequency and patterns of use, tag usage, feedback request trends, etc. (“Aggregated Data”). CustomerGauge uses Aggregated Data as a statistical measure and not in a manner that would identify you personally. Aggregated Data enables us to determine how often certain parts of CustomerGauge’s Web site or the CustomerGauge Services are used so that we can improve them. CustomerGauge may make use of, or make such Aggregated Data available to, third parties, in any manner in our sole discretion.

 **Social Media Features:  **The CustomerGauge Web sites may use Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on our Web site and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. You may be given the option by such Social Media Features to post information about your activities on this Web site to a profile page of yours that is provided by a third party Social Media network in order to share with others within your network. Social Media Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing the relevant Social Media Features.

 **Survey Features:  **Cookies are not stored for CustomerGauge Survey Users. The survey system may collect IP address, time, and other information shared by your browser in addition to any answers you may give.

 **5\. Public Forums, Refer a Friend, Reviews and Customer Testimonials**

CustomerGauge may provide bulletin boards, blogs, or chat rooms on the Company’s Web sites. Any Personal Information you choose to submit in such a forum may be read, collected, or used by others who visit these forums, and may be used to send you unsolicited messages. CustomerGauge is not responsible for the Personal Information you choose to submit in these forums.

CustomerGauge posts a list of Customers and testimonials on the Company’s Web sites that contain information such as Customer names and titles.

CustomerGauge provides Review sites for Clients and contingent on additional consent by Survey Users may publish comments and other information.

 **6\. Sharing of Information Collected**

 **Service Providers** CustomerGauge may share Data About CustomerGauge Customers with the Company’s contracted service providers, such a payment processors, so that these service providers can provide services on our behalf. CustomerGauge may also share Data About CustomerGauge Customers with the Company’s service providers to ensure the quality of information provided. Unless described in this Privacy Statement, CustomerGauge does not share, sell, rent, or trade any information with third parties for their promotional purposes.

 **CustomerGauge Affiliates** The Company may share Data About CustomerGauge Customers with other companies in order to work with them, including affiliates of the CustomerGauge corporate group. For example, the Company may need to share Data About CustomerGauge Customers for customer relationship management purposes.

 **Business Partners** From time to time, CustomerGauge may partner with other companies to jointly offer products or services. If you purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly-offered product or service from CustomerGauge, the Company may share Data About CustomerGauge Customers collected in connection with your purchase or expression of interest with our joint promotion partner(s). CustomerGauge does not control our business partners’ use of the Data About CustomerGauge Customers we collect, and their use of the information will be in accordance with their own privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this manner, you may opt not to purchase or specifically express interest in a jointly offered product or service.

 **Billing** CustomerGauge may use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use Billing Information except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on the Company’s behalf.

 **Compelled Disclosure** CustomerGauge reserves the right to use or disclose information provided if required by law or if the Company reasonably believes that use or disclosure is necessary to protect the Company’s rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.

 **7\. International Transfer of Information Collected**

To facilitate CustomerGauge’s global operations, the Company may transfer and access Data About CustomerGauge Customers from around the world, including the United States. This Privacy Statement shall apply even if CustomerGauge transfers Data About CustomerGauge Customers to other countries.

For European visitors to the CustomerGauge Web site and users of the CustomerGauge Services, please note that in order to provide the information or services requested, your Personal Information may be transferred outside of the European Economic Area (“EEA”). By visiting the CustomerGauge Web site or using the CustomerGauge Services, you agree to CustomerGauge transferring your Personal Information outside the EEA. Certain clients have agreements with CustomerGauge that their own client data is not transferred outside the EEA and information on this can be obtained in writing from CustomerGauge.

 **8\. Communications Preferences**

CustomerGauge offers Visitors and Customers who provide contact information a means to choose how the Company uses the information provided. You may manage your receipt of marketing and non-transactional communications by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link located on the bottom of the Company’s emails. Additionally, you may send a request specifying your communications preferences to [support@customergauge.com](mailto:support@customergauge.com) . Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with CustomerGauge or the Services.

 **9\. Correcting and Updating Your Information**

Website Users are entitled to understand how CustomerGauge uses their data, and can make information or deletion requests to [mailto:legal@customergauge.com](mailto:legal@customergauge.com). CustomerGauge is fully compliant with GDPR Legislation. We may refer you to the Data Controller for further action (see section 11).

Customers may update or change their registration information by editing their user or organization record. To update a user profile, please login to [CustomerGauge](https://login.customergauge.com/) with your CustomerGauge username and password and edit your user settings.

To update Billing Information or have your registration information deleted, please email [support@customergauge.com](mailto:support@customergauge.com).  To discontinue your account, please email [support@customergauge.com](mailto:support@customergauge.com).

Requests to access, change, or delete your information will be handled within 30 days.

 **10\. Data Retention**

CustomerGauge retains the information we receive as described in this Privacy Statement, as well as the Customer Data we process on behalf of our Customers (as defined below), for reasonable duration, for example, as the case may be, for as long as needed to provide our Services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, establish legal defenses, to conduct audits, pursue legitimate business purposes, and enforce our agreements.

 **11\. Customer Data**

As part of using our Services, Customers (“Data Controllers”) may submit electronic data or information to the Services (“Customer Data”) that constitutes Personal Information of other individuals (Survey Users) to us.  Such data may include an individual’s name, email address, or phone number.  CustomerGauge acts as “Data Processor” for our Customers, and generally has no direct relationship with the individuals to whom Customer Data may pertain. Any uses of Customer Data by the Company are done so pursuant to CustomerGauge’s Terms of Service or a subscription agreement in place between CustomerGauge and the relevant Customer (or his/her organization), and may include a GDPR-Compliant Data Processing Agreement which exclusively govern CustomerGauge’s treatment of Customer Data and supersede this Privacy Statement in case of conflict, or as required by law.  If Personal Information pertaining to you as an individual has been submitted to us by a Customer as Customer Data and you wish to exercise any rights you may have to access, correct, amend, or delete such data, please inquire with the Customer (or his/her organization) directly. If an authorized Customer requests that we update or remove the data in question and he or she has no ability to do so via use of the Services, we will acknowledge their request within 30 days.

 **12\. Security**

CustomerGauge takes precautions, including administrative, technical, and physical measures – to help safeguard Data against loss, theft, and misuse as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. While we follow generally accepted standards to protect information submitted to us, including the use of secure socket layer (SSL) technology, no method of storage or transmission is 100% secure.

Users are solely responsible for protecting their passwords, limiting access to their computers, and signing out of the CustomerGauge Services after their sessions.

 **13\. Changes to this Privacy Statement**

CustomerGauge reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. CustomerGauge will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Statement through the Company’s Web sites at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.

 **14\. Contacting Us**

Questions regarding this Privacy Statement or the information practices of the Company’s Web sites should be directed to CustomerGauge Privacy at legal@customergauge.com or by mailing CustomerGauge Privacy (c/o CustomerGauge/Directness BV), van Diemenstraat 182b, Amsterdam 1013CP, The Netherlands.
